<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tips on agus sarwono - programming for dummies</title>
    <link>https://agussarwono.com/categories/tips/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tips on agus sarwono - programming for dummies</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 09:30:00 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://agussarwono.com/categories/tips/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bore - Simple open source tunnel to localhost</title>
      <link>https://agussarwono.com/article/bore-simple-open-source-tunnel-to-localhost/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 09:30:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://agussarwono.com/article/bore-simple-open-source-tunnel-to-localhost/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will learn how to expose your local development using bore as ngrok open source alternative&#xA;Sometimes, when we do local development, we might need to expose our local development URL to the public. For example, we might need to test and access it from a mobile device. Instead of using an IP address, we can use the URL generated by tools like ngrok or localtunnel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplified Guide Setting Up a Local Domain with Caddy Server</title>
      <link>https://agussarwono.com/article/setting-up-a-local-domain-with-caddy-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 09:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://agussarwono.com/article/setting-up-a-local-domain-with-caddy-server/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the realm of web development and local testing environments, creating custom local domain can streamline the devepment process. this guide walks you the steps to set up a new local domain using Caddy Server&#xA;Prerequisites CaddyServer: make sure you have caddy installed on your system, if you haven&amp;rsquo;t installed it yet, You can download and install it from the official Caddy website&#xA;Text Editor (vscode,vim, etc&amp;hellip;), have a text editor of your choice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Menikmati segelas air hangat</title>
      <link>https://agussarwono.com/article/segelas-air-hangat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://agussarwono.com/article/segelas-air-hangat/</guid>
      <description>Salah satu kebiasaan yang saya lakukan di pagi hari adalah minum air hangat, terutama jika ditambahkan sedikit rasa manis. Selain dapat menyegarkan tubuh dan pikiran, minum air di pagi hari sangat baik untuk kesehatan, terutama jika yang diminum adalah air putih.&#xA;Setiap harinya, kita sebaiknya mengonsumsi sekitar 2 liter air untuk memenuhi kebutuhan cairan dalam tubuh.&#xA;Dulu, setiap kali saya ingin meminum air hangat, saya menggunakan dispenser air dengan fitur pemanasan otomatis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prepend your commit with JIRA ticket number</title>
      <link>https://agussarwono.com/article/add-ticket-to-your-commit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 09:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://agussarwono.com/article/add-ticket-to-your-commit/</guid>
      <description>summary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cast an interface/struct in golang</title>
      <link>https://agussarwono.com/article/cast-interface-struct-golang/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 15:45:42 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://agussarwono.com/article/cast-interface-struct-golang/</guid>
      <description>type casting interface in golang can be useful when you build a modular app using golang&#xA;says package main import ( &amp;#34;fmt&amp;#34; ) type Bird interface { Fly() } type Parrot struct { Bird Name string } func (p *Parrot) Fly() { fmt.Println(&amp;#34;a Parrot name &amp;#34; + p.Name + &amp;#34; flying&amp;#34;) } type Dove struct { Bird Name string } func (p *Dove) Fly() { fmt.Println(&amp;#34;a Dove name &amp;#34; + p.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
