<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Programming on agus sarwono - programming for dummies</title><link>//0.0.0.0:1313/categories/programming/</link><description>Recent content in Programming on agus sarwono - programming for dummies</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//0.0.0.0:1313/categories/programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Build Configurable Running Text using NodeMCU + Arduino IDE + P10 Dot Matrix using DMDESP + WEBSOCKET</title><link>//0.0.0.0:1313/article/building-running-text-using-nodemcu-arduino-p10/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//0.0.0.0:1313/article/building-running-text-using-nodemcu-arduino-p10/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="minesweeper">Minesweeper&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>In this tutorial i will guide you to how to build a Running Text Display using P10 Single Color Dot Matrix and a NodeMCU.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>getting started&lt;/p>
&lt;p>creating grid&lt;/p>
&lt;p>placing bomb&lt;/p>
&lt;p>placing number&lt;/p>
&lt;p>clearing tiles&lt;/p>
&lt;p>adding flag&lt;/p>
&lt;p>winning&lt;/p>
&lt;p>wrap up&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Build your own snake game</title><link>//0.0.0.0:1313/article/build-your-own-snake-game/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 09:37:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>//0.0.0.0:1313/article/build-your-own-snake-game/</guid><description>&lt;p>In this tutorial we will learn how to create a snake game in lua using love2d
snake game was one of the nostalic game you ever play,&lt;/p>
&lt;p>by the end of this tutorial you will learn to&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Create a snake&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Create a food for snake&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Move the snake&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;h4 id="the-classical">The Classical&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>I know all af you have played Snake on your Phone, and in this tutorial i will show you as a techie, how to build your simple own snake game&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Create your own minesweeper game</title><link>//0.0.0.0:1313/article/build-your-own-minesweeper/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 09:37:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>//0.0.0.0:1313/article/build-your-own-minesweeper/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="minesweeper">Minesweeper&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Welcome to this tutorial on building your very own Minesweeper game using the LÖVE framework and Lua programming language. Minesweeper is a classic puzzle game that challenges players to clear a grid of hidden mines using logic and deduction. By the end of this tutorial, you will have a fully functional Minesweeper game and a deeper understanding of game development concepts.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In this step-by-step guide, we will cover everything from setting up your development environment to implementing game mechanics such as grid creation, bomb placement, and user interactions. Whether you are a beginner or an experienced developer, this tutorial will provide you with the knowledge and skills needed to create a fun and engaging game.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>