<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Experiences on agus sarwono - programming for dummies</title>
    <link>https://agussarwono.com/experience/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Experiences on agus sarwono - programming for dummies</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://agussarwono.com/experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Senior Frontend Engineer</title>
      <link>https://agussarwono.com/experience/fe-sfe-okadoc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://agussarwono.com/experience/fe-sfe-okadoc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Results-oriented frontend developer with a proven track record of building scalable and user-friendly web applications. Expert in React and other modern frontend frameworks. Collaborate seamlessly with cross-functional teams to translate business needs into innovative digital solutions. Passionate about delivering exceptional user experiences on the Okadoc platform.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frontend Lead</title>
      <link>https://agussarwono.com/experience/fe-lead-mm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://agussarwono.com/experience/fe-lead-mm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I enjoy collaborating with teams to design and implement innovative software solutions, with a passion for frontend development and user experience, always looking for opportunities to improve efficiency and productivity.  I have contributed to the successful deployment of scalable and reliable software products and have experience leading and motivating teams.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mataharimall.com (discontinued)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mataharistore.com (discontinued)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Frontend Engineer</title>
      <link>https://agussarwono.com/experience/fe-sfe-mm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://agussarwono.com/experience/fe-sfe-mm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a Fullstack Engineer at Mataharimall.com, I played a key role in maintaining and enhancing their monolithic e-commerce application built with the PHP Phalcon Framework.  I collaborated closely with the backend team on the migration to a microservice architecture. This experience provided valuable full-stack development skills and fostered my ability to collaborate effectively within a large engineering team.  I then transitioned to specializing in Frontend Engineering.&#xA;Since then, I&amp;rsquo;ve become a seasoned Frontend Engineer with a proven track record of delivering high-quality e-commerce solutions. I have a strong history of collaborating effectively with cross-functional teams to translate business requirements into innovative and user-friendly web experiences. My expertise includes responsive design, performance optimization, and modern web technologies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
