<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tutorial on agus sarwono - programming for dummies</title><link>https://agussarwono.com/tags/tutorial/</link><description>Recent content in Tutorial on agus sarwono - programming for dummies</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 09:30:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://agussarwono.com/tags/tutorial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bore: The Open-Source Tool for Effortless Localhost Tunneling</title><link>https://agussarwono.com/article/ssh-tunneling/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 09:30:00 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://agussarwono.com/article/ssh-tunneling/</guid><description>Introduction In this article, we will learn how to expose your local development using bore as ngrok open source alternative
Sometimes, when we do local development, we might need to expose our local development URL to the public. For example, we might need to test and access it from a mobile device. Instead of using an IP address, we can use the URL generated by tools like ngrok or localtunnel.</description></item><item><title>Simple blog api using python flask and markdown</title><link>https://agussarwono.com/article/simple-blog-api-using-python-flask-and-markdown/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 12:56:36 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://agussarwono.com/article/simple-blog-api-using-python-flask-and-markdown/</guid><description>I have a blog generated by Hugo, and I require access to its content through a REST API. Due to Hugo&amp;rsquo;s nature as a static site generator and not a server, it lacks a native feature for exposing a REST API.
Upon further investigation, I found that I can develop a Python script using the Flask framework to create a JSON-compatible REST API for accessing my blog&amp;rsquo;s content. While it may seem unconventional to use Flask instead of generating a JSON file directly in Hugo, I view this as an opportunity to enhance my proficiency in Python.</description></item></channel></rss>